# IFEOLUWA DELE-OYERO

- **J** 08146917848
- deleoyeroifeoluwa@gmail.com
- Lekki-Ajah, Lagos 101003

#### SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- ReactStrap
- CSS3
- Chakraui
- HTML5
- MaterialUi

# LANGUAGES

**English-language**, Fluent Yoruba-Language

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-focused Frontend Developer with experience in web-based applications and Software Solutions. Participated in development and implementation of Apps, Logical and results-driven Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused Solutions for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with calm and focused demeanor.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### FRONTEND ENGINEER INTERN (REMOTE)

**T40 Technologies** 

Lagos, Lagos

April 2022 - Current

- Developing Scalable Uis using Reactjs and React-strap framework
- Consume Endpoints (APIs) and integrate on the User-End
- Deploy Logic and Fix user-e4nd related Bugs
- Deploy codes on Bitbuckets and perform series of Git operations

#### FRONTEND ENGINEER

Zealight Lab Innovations

lekki, Lagos Nigeria

April 2022 - Current

- Developing Scalable UIs using Reactjs Framework
- Consume Endpoints (APIs) and integrate on the USer-End
- Fixing of Bugs
- Deploy codes on Bitbuckets and GitHub
- Completed technical development and application tasks per approved project standards and allocated budgets.

### FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

Skill Up Africa

Lekki, Lagos

August 2021 - March 2022

 Learnt and used modern tools and technologies for frontEnd web development. - Created responsive web applications using Reactjs. - learnt and maximized the use of third partyAPI.

## **EDUCATION**

#### NATIONAL DIPLOMA: COMPUTER SCIENCE

The Polytechnic Ibadan Ibadan, oyo-state

# HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA: COMPUTER SCIENCE

The Polytechnic Ibadan Ibadan, Oyo-State